

# Jaewon Lee

ROBOTICS · MULTI-ROBOT · SLAM

25, Galmaejungang-ro, Guri-si, Gyeonggi-do, 11902, Rep. of KOREA

 $\ \square$  (+82) 10-9114-2756 |  $\ \blacksquare$  ashcircle@kw.ac.kr |  $\ \blacksquare$  lee-jaewon.github.io |  $\ \boxdot$  Lee-JaeWon

"Passion is the genesis of genius."

# **Summary**

This is Jaewon Lee, who wants to be a Robotics researcher and engineer. I am interested in Robotics, SLAM, Multi-Robot System. I think Robotics can help the development of the world a lot. I want to study a lot and approach the world.

# Research Interests

Multi-RobotSLAM, Loop Closing, Pose EstimationSLAMLiDAR-Inertial SLAM, Localization

# Education

Yonsei University Seoul, S.Korea

Integrated M.S./Ph.D. in Electrical and Electronic Engineering (Advisor:Prof.Euntai Kim)

Mar. 2024(Expected) -

#### **KwangWoon University**

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

Mar. 2020 - Feb. 2024

CDA 4 11 /4 FO M -: - - CDA 4 3

• GPA: 4.11/4.50, Major GPA: 4.28/4.50

• Club: BARAM Robotics (Robotics Academic Group) - [2022 Vice President], Mar.2020-Feb.2024

# **Work Experience**

CILAB @Yonsei Univ

Undergraduate LAB Intern (Advisor : PROF. Euntai Kim)

Jul. 2023 - Present

• Multi Robot System

· LiDAR Inertial SLAM

ROBOMATION Seoul, S,Korea

**R&D Intern**Jun. 2022 - Aug. 2022

• I developed an automation system for soccer games using multi-robot.

• I developed multi-robot coordination and pose system using Aruco Marker.

#### Robotics A.I. LAB. @KwangWoon Univ

Seoul, S.Kored

Undergraduate LAB Intern (Advisor: PROF. Junghyun Oh)

Jan. 2022 - Jun. 2022

- I studied visual SLAM and visual odometry
- I studied Multi-Robot system and implemented Multi-Robot exploration

## Honors & Awards

## **AWARDS**

2023.12 <b>2023 Hanium ICT Mentoring Competition</b> , Silver Award	Ministry of Science
	and ICT, IITP, FKii

2023.10 ICCV 2023 SLAM Challenge,
Fourth place in LiDAR-Inertial Track - Taeyoung Kim, <u>Jaewon Lee</u>, Beomsoo Kim, Euntai Kim

2023.06 **Undergraduate Paper Award**, Paper - Autonomous multi robot parking system

2022.10 **Dean's list**, for Academic Excellence Kwangwoon Univ.

#### **HONORS**

2022.10 **Full Tuition Scholarship**, for the first place in last semester *Kwangwoon Univ.* 

# **Publication**

#### **DOMESTIC CONFERENCE**

"Autonomous Multi Robot Parking System", 2023.06

Jaewon Lee, Hyosuk Joo, Chung-gil Ahn, Hyedo Kim, Junghyun Oh - [Paper]

# Skills\_

**Programming** C++/C, Python, MATLAB DevOps ROS/ROS2, Docker, Git

**Framework** PyTorch, Tensorflow, Keras, Unity

# **Extracurricular Activity**

#### Technical Blog - lee-jaewon.github.io

Jul. 2021 - Present

WRITER

• I have been writing posts about the paper review, development, the study of Interests.

- · To study through writing and sharing.
- The blog is available at [here].

#### Technical Team Blog - ropiens.tistory.com

Jul. 2022 - Present

CO-WRITER

- I have been writing posts about the paper review, development, the study of Interests.
- To study through writing and sharing.
- The blog is available at [here].

## **Autonomous Multi Robot Parking System**

CAPSTONE DESIGN

Jan.2023 - Jun.2023

- Implement a multi-robot system and implement various technologies necessary for mobile robots.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

# 2022 Open Source Contribution Academy

MENTEE

I contributed to translating PyTorch Hub English documents into Korean at the PyTorch Korean User's Group.

#### **Multi Robot Collision Avoidance with Velocity Obstacle**

Jul. 2022 - Oct. 2022

PERSONAL PROJECT

Sep.2022 - Nov.2022

- I implemented collision avoidance with Velocity Obstacle using multi-robot.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

### **Autonomous Driving Simulation with Reinforcement Learning**

PERSONAL PROJECT

PERSONAL PROJECT

Sep.2021 - Nov.2021

- · I implemented an Autonomous-driving system through DQN algorithm for the high-way situation.
- I implemented a simulator with Unity. And I managed the reward using Laser Sensor.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

#### Frontier Based Multi-Robot Exploration

Mar.2022 - Jun.2022

Mar.2022 - Jun.2022

• Limplemented ROS-based multi-robot frontier exploration.

- I implemented a multi-robot SLAM system using open sources.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].

## **House Interior Classifier and Automatic Recommendation**

DEEP-LEARNING PROJECT

• I implemented House Interior Classifier using Inception-Resnet-V2 in Keras.

- · I implemented a system that can automatically search on the actual shopping site with the classified result.
- The source code for the project is available at [my GitHub repository].